Ser Ryam was an excellent Lord Commander of the Kingsguard.
But he was sick. I hope he died in peace.
Yes, your grace. He died in his sleep.
The Silent Sisters prepare their remains.
His successor, Ser Harrold, would like to meet
A replacement for Ser Ryam in the Guard.
Your grace, my lords.
The Kingsguard needs to find its seventh member.
With the help of the Hand of the King, I invited candidates to court.
They all gave an excellent proof of themselves.
Four ships lost!
One carried my flag.
The Stepstones are on fire,
And you stand here babbling.
If you want to talk about it...
I worry about the future
Of my ships and my men.
The Crown will compensate you and make you an offer
The families.
I don't want to be compensated.
I want to take control of the Stepstones by force, and chase away the crab chow.
I will not go to war with the Free Cities.
These pirates are not part of it.
Who do you think provides them with ships and supplies?
Throughout its history,
The Seven Kingdoms never fought the Free Cities.
If that happen,
The losses would be immense.
Why does crab feeding fear us?
The king's brother has taken Dragonstone and protects it
With their golden robes.
Daemon planted himself there
For more than six months.
And the crown doesn't lift an eyelash.
Be careful, Lord Corlys.
A seat at the king's table doesn't make him like you.
I do what I could do,
And sent emissaries to Pentos
And to Volantis to find common cause.
Ships and men will be mobilized.
The Stepstones issue will be resolved..
In due time.
You have dragon riders, father.
Envy us.
The matter is not so simple, Rhaenyra.
It would be a show of force.
At least the princess has a plan.
I'm just saying that we should...
It might be ...
We could make the most of it
Of the resources the princess talks about.
Take her to see the Lord Commander candidates.
Good idea, your grace.
this knight
It will also ensure your protection. Then you must choose it.
Sor Desmond Caron.
A skilled knight, princess.
Please go ahead.
Son of Ser Royce Caron, Ser Desmond proved his strength
In and out of tournaments.
He recently crossed the Bosco del Re
And delivered a hunter
the Justice.
Thank him for his faithful service.
Thank you for your loyal service to the Crown, ser.
Sor Rymun Mallister
Son of Lord Lymond Mallister of Seagard.
Cider scrum winner.
Last left in the saddle.. of 23 riders.
Rider since the age of 18.
How many of these knights have battle experience?
Excluding hunters.
Sor Criston Cole.
the attendant's son
From the Lord of Blackhaven.
Welcome, Ser Criston.
Did you fight in the stormlands?
In the Lowlands of Dorne, princess.
A year of infantry to repel the Dornishmen.
Ser Dondarrion knighted me after a success in the Bones.
I choose to be Criston Cole.
Let's not make a hasty decision, princess.
Ser Criston is undoubtedly a valiant warrior,
But the Crakehalls and Mallisters are important allies of the Crown.
Seagart, for example, is our main protection against the Iron Islands.
These men are tournament drivers.
My father needs a man who fought the battle to protect him.
Do not you think?
That's right, princess.
So let's get ready
For the investiture of Ser Criston.
The capital of Valyria was built on a volcano,
Just like Dragonstone.
The dragon lords, flower of nobility,
They lived here, next to a volcano.
Close to the source of your magic and power.
There was Anogrion.
Blood mages practiced their art there.
What you've built... is wonderful.
Oh, I only study history and I provide the plans for the crown.
Masons build the buildings.
Will Westeros become another Valyria?
It depends
Whether you talk about the empire during its heyday..or its downfall.
A thousand dragons, a fleet that covered
All the seas of the world.
Valyria's glory will never be equaled.
To the Seven Underworlds!
- How's it going with Rhaenyra? - What do you mean?
These days, he barely talks to me.
It might be hard for her
Unburden your heart.
Just need time.
I needed it when my mother died.
I wish it would come to me and...
Why not the other way around?
Sometimes I'd rather face the Dark Terror
Than my fifteen-year-old daughter.
I think she would trust you if you asked her.
You are so good to hear, Your Grace.
Rhaenyra doesn't know anything about our conversation, does she?
I mean ...
I don't think he would understand.
No, your grace.
It's been 6 months since my mother died,
And they already want my father to marry and find another heir.
I know these men
They were secretly plotting when I was sent away.
Don't worry about lord and king's business.
Let's say your father remarried...
Your father loves you.
He chose you as his heir.
He didn't choose me... he rejected Daemon.
Kneel with me.
It's the only way I can be with my mother.
In the silence of the Temple of the Seven,
I feel close to her.
It's stupid, I know.
I don't think it's stupid.
No way.
Everything is fine.
You could try.
If you don't do it for me, do it for them.
What should I speak?
Anything you want.
It's between the gods and you.
I want you to see me as something other than your daughter.
Even my father doesn't understand us, women.
When I want to talk to him,
I always have to take the first step.
Thanks.
Your grace, thank you for coming.
I know tempers are on fire today.
I attach great importance to the bond that unites our homes.
Rhaenys is my favorite cousin.
I want to apologize
For the remarks made during the restricted council.
I didn't mean to offend you.
Your fleet is an important asset to the kingdom.
But you understand that my duty as king..
It is to avoid war as long as possible.
Nobody wants open war.
May I speak sincerely, Your Grace?
I appreciate the candor of my advisors.
I fear the enemy's eyes
They are currently fixed in the Red Keep.
The queen is dead.
A woman was named heir for the first time.
The king's brother took over Dragonstone
Without any opposition.
And a foreign power is occupying our main sea lane.
This is a very sad image of my kingdom.
It's the harsh reality
Prima.
The Crown is seen as vulnerable.
And a blind foray into the Steps..
Would it prove otherwise?
To ride a storm,
Either we run towards it, or we go around it.
But we never wait for their attacks.
What conduct do you propose to adopt,
my Lord?
We unite our families.
Marry our daughter, Laena.
Let's unite the two great houses of Valyria.
Binding your dragons to our fleet with blood,
You will determine that the glory of your kingdom is in the days to come,
Not in the past.
I have to recognize..
That I had never thought about getting married again.
Aemma died just 6 months ago.
Sooner or later you will have to find a new wife, Your Grace, the realm expects that.
To strengthen your lineage and produce heirs.
There is no better person than Laena.
we talked a little
Since when ...
Much to my regret.
We must be free to speak openly.
You are free to speak whenever you want,
You are the king.
I loved your mother..
With all my heart.
Me too.
Ser Harrold has gathered brave knights.
But I talked to them
And Ser Criston is the only one who has ever really fought in battle.
He will shine in the Kingsguard.
During the little council...
Don't think about it anymore.
- I thought I might... - You're young.
You will learn.
This is our best chance to save your finger, Sire.
The worms will remove the necrotic flesh
And rot.
I just granted Lord Corlys an audience
E para Rhaenys.
Very kind of you.
Lord Corlys must have appreciated this gesture of mine.
He proposed a marriage to me.
With whom, Your Grace?
Miss Leana.
To join the forces of our homes
And establish that the glory of my kingdom is yet to come,
And it still hasn't passed.
It was presumptuous on the part of Lord Corlys, Your Grace.
This matter should be discussed
To the restricted council.
That's what I'm doing.
Then ..
What do you advise me, my dear Otto?
Mrs Leana
She is very young, Your Grace.
True, but the problems that arose in the Grand Council remain.
marry their daughter
It would help a lot to resolve the outstanding issues.
And the alliance of two great houses
It would be a sign of unity
To the kingdom.. and beyond.
The Grand Master's argument is valid.
- But I fear Rhaenyra's reaction. - Why, my lord?
Your mother died.
Your father has to take care of the succession, that's normal.
Myself...
I loved my wife deeply.
The pain of his death still haunts me.
Being forced to remarry
to replace you
In the name of duty...
you are the king,
But I don't envy you..
How was the Black Terror?
You were the last to ride Balerion.
Just for a short time, before dying.
Its extinction marked the end of ancient Valyria.
Vhagar is still alive.
Somewhere ..
It's too big for the Dragon Pit.
Some would say it's too big even for our world.
Do you know where he nestled?
What you mean to say?
Do you know where Vhagar is now?
According to the dragon guardians, it should be somewhere on the shores of the Narrow Sea.
In the Port of Ibben, we sometimes hear his song..
They say it's sad.
Loneliness also affects dragons.
It would be an honor for me,
Unite our houses as in the times of ancient Valyria.
I will have children of pure Valyrian blood
To strengthen the royal bloodline, and with it the kingdom.
These are your father's words.
What did your mother tell you?
That I wouldn't sleep with you until I was 14.
It bothers you, right?
My father is the King.
He must remarry and strengthen the bloodline.
I asked if you mind.
Laena is your daughter. Does that bother you?
Clear.
But I understand the order of things.
I doubt this is your case.
If your intention was to arouse my anger,
Know that you have failed, princess.
On the contrary.
let it be my daughter
or someone else, your father will have a new wife.
will generate new heirs
And one of them will inevitably be a boy.
When he comes of age,
You will be considered the heir to the throne, not you.
Because that's the order of things.
Once queen, I will disturb you.
I wish it were possible.
But the kingdom could have appointed a queen to the Great Council of Harrenhal.
He rejected the idea.
They rejected you, Princess Rhaenys
"The Queen Who Wasn't"
Not the idea of ​​a female queen, in fact those same men bowed to me.
And do you remember them bringing them the wine?
Here's the hard truth that no one dared to tell you.
Men would give fire and blood to the kingdom
Instead of seeing a woman rule.
Your father is not naive.
The Select Council urges me to remarry.
The kingdom asks for a new queen.
A kind and generous queen will reassure her subjects.
The select council suggested a name
Lady Corlys
He offered me his daughter's hand.
Miss Leana.
An excellent choice, Your Grace.
I confess I don't know her very well.
She is undoubtedly sweet and generous.
He will enjoy your company, as I will.
I brought a gift.
I asked for it to be fixed.
Your ..
A nice gesture from you, Alicent.
Very kind.
In between.
The King's Hand, Your Grace.
I urgently convened the little council.
For what reason?
You better see it directly.
Great.
It was when the night was dark, at the time of the bat.
The thief escaped our pursuit.
How did you manage to steal a dragon egg
under the eyes of 50 guards?
It was Prince Daemon who took it, Lord.
The prince
He left a missive that contains
One explanation.
"It is with pleasure
That I, Daemon Targaryen,
Prince of Dragonstone and rightful heir
From the Iron Throne,
I inform you that I am about to have a second wife,
As in the days of ancient Valyria.
will take the title
From Lady Mysaria of Dragonstone.
Your Grace is pregnant. Also, a dragon egg
Will be placed in the crib, as tradition dictates
From House Targaryen. "
The prince
He invited you to his wedding, sir.
In two days.
Gods have mercy.
Who is this lady Mysaria?
- We think it's... - You whore.
This is an act of sedition.
I agree.
My brother
Try to provoke me.
He waits for my reaction.
The kingdom is watching, sir.
What should I do?
Send him to the Wall?
Stick your head on a pike?
Daemon conquered Deago Rock, surrounded by his golden cloaks
And stole a scary weapon.
What egg did Daemon steal?
o of Dreamfyre, princess.
the one you chose for Prince Baelon's birthplace.
Collect a supply, Otto.
I'm going to Dragonstone.
- I'll bring Daemon back. - Your grace.
Sorry, I can't agree with that. It's very dangerous.
Daemon is out of control.
Let me go to Dragonstone.
You are absolutely sublime.
Why are you pampering yourself like this?
Do you see the king tonight?
If yes you want.
- Good morning, Ser Criston. - My lady.
I've gathered your top 20 guards, Lord Main.
Ser Harrold will accompany us.
Take care of the Hand, Ser Criston.
Welcome to Dragonstone, Otto.
Your stay on this island is about to end.
Return the dragon egg, dismiss your army,
banish your whore
And let Dragonstone,
By order of the king...
Where?
- ..I don't see it. - Your Majesty
He would never approve of games like that.
Ser Crispin, correct?
Sor Criston Cole.
Sorry. She had escaped me.
Like the day I knocked you out in the tournament?
Great.
What a heartbreaking sight, Daemon
To get the king's attention, are you acting like a populin simpleton?
I simply follow the traditions of my home, just like my brother is doing.
Traditions apply to real children,
Not for bastards born to any whore.
- Lady Mysaria is my future wife - It's despicable.
You profane your name,
Your house and the king.
Love ignores titles and traditions.
And you men of the Guard
You are helping a traitor
The king appointed me commander, my golden robes are faithful to me.
You came for the egg.
Here it is.
You are crazy?
You will never survive rebelling like this.
Neither you.
Choose violence,
It would be to declare war
To your king.
It is wonderful.
Even if you are the recipient of losing your unborn child and mother?
Guards!
Set the blades aside.
- What are you doing? - I avoid a bloodbath.
Ser Criston, bring the princess to safety.
Don't panic Syrax.
He fiercely protects me.
My father made me princess of Dragon Stone.
It is my castle that you occupy my uncle.
It will be yours when you come of age.
You upset your king.
And how did I annoy him?
Today I celebrate my wedding.
You already have a wife.
That I didn't choose.
And that's why you had to steal my brother's egg?
A dragon shared its cradle.
It will be the same for my son.
Will you be a father?
One day.
Here I am in front of you, uncle.
The object of your wrath.
The reason for your disinheritance.
If you want to be the heir, you'll have to kill me.
So do it.
Put an end to these inconveniences.
You announced our marriage
Tomorrow.
And I was expecting a baby
Your baby.
When we get married, that can happen.
I did what it took to never have to give birth.
Well, kids are annoying.
You swore to protect me.
Dragonstone is a safe place.
Until the king claims the seat of his ancestors.
Your men will not kill the prince,
But what will they do with the whore he says he married
And who is pregnant?
Nobody will touch you.
I've been sold numerous times.
Since my birth.. in a land I forgot.
I lived most of my days in terror.
You are safe with me.
You are a Targaryen.
You can have fun teasing the king.
But I do not.
I'm not with you for the gold,
For your power,
or the color of your hair.
I just wanted to be released.
released?
Of what?
From fear.
Please, Lorde Lyonel.
I seek an honest opinion.
I wouldn't be able to do anything else.
Since my name was spoken at the Great Council,
I feel Corlys Velaryon's envious gaze on me,
Across the black waters
You are the highest rank in the kingdom.
The envious I can see what they want.
Laena Velaryon.
Lord Corlys is the commander of your ship.
Laena is the oldest in the richest house
Of Kingdom.
He comes from impeccable Valyrian stock.
And he has Targaryen blood.
What would be the problem?
She is only 12 years old.
But it will grow.
I don't want to get married again.
As king, some things need to be done.
Like it or not.
You will not escape marriage.
And if I refuse your proposal
He can take it wrong.
Apart from a direct link to the throne, nothing will satisfy you.
Keep in mind the shadow of war hanging over the Stepstones.
The Sea Serpent owns half of our fleet.
He would not deprive the kingdom of his support.
- Who is he to deceive me? - Nobody.
However, Lamarck is a better ally than an enemy.
Corlys' gesture is calculated and natural
For a man of his position.
- You want an honest opinion... - Yes.
Marry Laena Velaryon, Your Grace.
Heed Lord Corlys' request and secure his support.
Once and for all.
Your grace.
The princess has returned from Dragonstone.
From Dragonstone?
Your grace.
You disobeyed me.
You fled Port-Réal without saying a word.
and you acted
Without the king's permission.
You are my only heir.
You could have been killed!
Can I seat?
You went to Dragonstone.
I took the egg without violence.
A feat Ser Otto could not have accomplished alone.
Yup. eh well...
I forget how much you look like her.
your mother's absence
It's a wound that will never heal.
Without her,
The Red Keep has lost a warmth it will never regain.
Glad to hear that from you.
And knowing that my grief is shared.
I wish I could have comforted you better after his death.
I had a hard time conceiving that my daughter was becoming a woman.
But I know
who understands
What is expected of me.
The king must take a wife.
I can never replace your mother.
And I will not change my line of succession.
But you are my only heir and our line of succession is fragile.
It can be broken easily.
By remarrying, I will be able to secure our protection.
Against who?
Who wants to challenge us.
I don't want to break our union.
You are the king.
Your supreme duty is to the kingdom.
Mom would understand.
Just as I understand.
hello, gentlemen
I decided to take a new wife.
I'm getting married...
com Lady Alicent Hightower,
Until late spring.
But it doesn't make any sense.
My house is of Valyrian descent.
The most powerful in the kingdom.
And I am your king.
Rhaenyra.
House Velaryon originated in the times of ancient Valyria.
It is older than House Targaryen,
According to some writings.
Unlike the Targaryens,
We were not dragon lords.
For centuries, my house drew its sustenance from the sea.
With tenacity and luck.
When I ascended the throne of Driftwood,
I knew what I wanted.
Then I understood.
Unlike other gentlemen,
I built my throne with sweat on my forehead.
I always thought that you and me
We were made of the same fabric.
I didn't know your brother was king.
We both have to chart our destinies.
We have been ignored far too often.
Did you take me to Driftmark to remind me of my post?
Or is there another reason?
A conflict shakes the Steps.
A Myrien prince
He feeds the sailors crabs.
I asked the king to send my fleet to this area.
But he refused.
It was never your forte.
Thing?
be king.
nutrigranchi has the support of the Free Cities
who would love to see Westeros weakened.
The king's lack of attention allowed him to gain strength.
If we lose these sea lanes,
My house will be shaken.
Driftmark won't fall while the king warms up
At feasts, dances and tournaments.
I'll talk to my brother whenever and however I want.
You are not going.
An attack on the Steps would allow you to
to prove its worth to those who doubt it.
We are the eldest children in the kingdom.
Our value is not taken for granted, it must be created.